

NIRAJ JADHAV

Email Marketing
Specialist

About Me

Revenue - driven sales & marketing professional with

Le 5 Years Experience as Email Marketing Specialist

Strategies to drive brand awareness and business

growth. Experience in creating and testing worldwide



Email marketing. 9970517403/7972159715



nirajjadhav55@gmail.com



Vishrantwadi, Pune - 411015

LANGUAGE

- English
- Hindi
- Marathi

SKILLS

- Campaign management
- Strategic planning
- Lead generation
- Customer Relationship
 Management (CRM)
- Analytics and Optimization
- Search Engine Optimization
- Evaluation of Marketing

 Campaigns
- Segmentation Strategies

EXPERIENCE

Adverticssoft It System Pvt.Ltd. Sept2018-Mar2023

Focusing on increasing ROI and CPM, SMTP server.

Monitored key performance metrics such as open rate, click-through rate, bounce rate, unsubscribe rate.

Ensured compliance with CAN-SPAM regulations in all email campaigns.

Plan and conduct A/B tests for different elements of email campaigns to optimize performance and improve key metrics.

Expanded customer base by successfully emailing prospects to enhance conversion rates.

Created and optimized email content for increased click-through rates Set up and manage email automation workflows using marketing automation platforms like Mailchimp, Hubspot, Apollo.io, Instantly.io.

Vovec Infotech Private Limited

Jun2018 - Aug2018

Generated reports on campaign performance for management review.

Analyzed customer data to create segmentation strategies for targeted emails.

Developed and implemented email marketing campaigns to increase customer engagement

Regenerative Medical Service Pvt.Ltd. Apr2016 - Jun2018

Maintained accurate records of all QC activities including test results, inspection data, corrective actions are taken.

Conducted quality testing of equipment to identify problems and arrange for repairs.

Monitored testing procedures to meet established item specifications, standard test methods or protocols.

EDUCATION

RTMNU Unviersity Nagpur

B-tech in Biotechnology 2011-2015

CERTIFICATIONS

Digital Marketer, Digitallion Aug 2022

Customer Relationship

Management, Great Learning Jan 2024

Customer Service Essentials, Great Learning Jan 2024